

Jimmy Cabuy

Web Developer • Digital Marketing Novice • Freelance Photographer

After graduating from EPHEC in e-business, I worked for over 2 years as a content creator, social media ads expert, and social media manager in a digital marketing agency. I then followed a web development Bootcamp in JavaScript to fulfil my dream of becoming a developer. Currently, I work at Decathlon Belgium as a front-end developer where I collabore to code, debug, troubleshoot, and enhance the website's user experience.

jimmycabuy@hotmail.com

Brussels

linkedin.com/in/jimmycabuy

+32/474.91.78.15

www.jimmy-cabuy.vercel.app

github.com/jimmycabuy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer

Decahtlon Belgium

06/2023 - Present

Brussels

Brussels

Technical Consultant

01/2023 - 06/2023 Brussels

Worldline 🗷

Financial Services

Social Media Manager

Socialsky 🗷

02/2019 - 06/2021 Social Media Agency

Achievements/Tasks

- Management of our clients' social networks
- Digital Strategy
- Social Ads
- Community Management

EDUCATION

General Humanities

Mater Dei

09/2009 - 06/2015 Brussels

Certificate of English

Browns English Language School

10/2015 - 12/2015 Brishane

Bachelor in e-Business

EPHEC ♂

09/2016 - 06/2019 Brussels

COURSES

- Web Development Web Design - Digital Marketing E-commerce

- Business Analyst - Supply Chain Management

Erasmus

ESSCA School of Management

08/2018 - 01/2019 Budanest

Web & Mobile Coding Bootcamp

La Capsule 🗷

03/2022 - 05/2022 Brussels

Courses

- HTML / CSS / JavaScript React.js - Express.js Node.is - MongoDB Heroku - UI Design - UX Design

SKILLS



TRAVELS

Australia (10/2015 - 05/2016)

America (07/2021 - 01/2022)

Canada, United-States, Mexico, Equator and Costa Rica

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Uwork (03/2022 - 05/2022) ♂

Uwork is a mobile application that connects jobseekers with companies looking for employees. This application aims to totally democratize and review the hiring system with a simple and easy to use application.

Portfolio - thedailyjim 🗗

In my spare time, I have another passion besides coding and another name: "thedailyjim" as a photographer. I've been passionate about the world of photography since I was young, and I love to get out of my house and capture the life and the surrounding landscapes.

CERTIFICATES

Web and Mobile Application Development Project Manager -Level 6

Svelte.js - The Complete Guide (incl. Sapper.js) Academind by Maximilian Schwarzmüller - 13 total hours

LANGUAGES

French English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Fitness Hockey Padel New technology **Tennis** Photography Travel Dogs